"We never forget what we endeavor to forget."
F.W. Nietzsche, "The Dawn of Day"
I've never thought of myself as
a good person or a bad person.
Since arriving at this school,
That's amazing, Honami-chan!
Oh, it really isn't...
I've sworn I'd face whatever
came at me head-on.
You're always so humble!
Student Council Room
Hey, Sakayanagi.
Yes, President Nagumo?
Does this student council
room even serve any purpose?
Couldn't we use it as a
karaoke box or something?
Wherever I am is the student council room.
That's a unique viewpoint.
So?
If you're not seeking entry
into the student council,
what is it that you want?
It regards the student council
officer, Ichinose Honami-san.
President Nagumo.
I'm about to mount an attack on her.
It could potentially result in her expulsion.
If it does, I beg your forbearance.
I thought I told you not to
escalate beyond bullying.
I was thinking of going a bit more extreme.
I was hoping to keep her
for my own amusement.
We must always account for the unexpected.
You're a bold girl.
3rd Season
Classroom
of
the
Elite
Classroom of
the Elite
Morning!
Oh, morning!
What's first period again?
So it's not because you have a
new boyfriend, Karuizawa-san?
It's math, dude.
I just felt like it was time
to come into my own.
It was just too easy to depend
on Yosuke-kun, you know?
Morning, Kiyotaka-kun!
Morning.
Hey.
Wow! That's so grown-up of you!
Things are lively in here today.
It appears Karuizawa-san
and Hirata-kun broke up.
And that's got the class all worked up?
You seemed close to both of them.
Were you aware?
Of course I wasn't.
I don't discuss their private lives.
Hey, Hirata!
I hear Karuizawa dumped you.
I suppose.
Hey, it's all good!
Knock it off, Yamauchi.
But a hot guy got dumped!
You gotta comfort the guy!
Sorry 'bout that.
Learn a little tact, man!
Lemme go, damn it!
How can you guys be so calm about it?
It's not that we're calm!
It's just kind of depressing.
Aw, you're so boring.
Good morning.
Would Yamauchi Haruki-kun be here, by chance?
Yeah, that's me.
Might I have a moment of your time?
Lemme go, dude.
O-Of course, I've got time!
Wh-What's going on here?!
The truth is, I've wanted to
speak with you for some time.
What? Really? For real?
She's going all-in.
It's a bit noisy here.
I'll meet you over there.
Over there?
No way, no way! This is impossible!
What's going on?
What's going on?!
Why in the world?
There's no mystery here.
Excuse me, Ike.
Wait just a minute, Yamauchi-kun.
What is it?
This is a trap.
Huh?
She has absolutely no reason
to want to talk to you.
What the hell does that mean?!
It does kinda sound like an insult, yeah.
Look, I'm only gonna say this once.
I am this class's lethal weapon.
What?
So it's gonna be fine!
Don't worry, I won't reveal
any sensitive info!
Sakayanagi-chan!
Does Sakayanagi-san really
like Yamauchi-kun?
What do you think, Kiyo-pon, Yukimoo?
I don't know much about that sort of thing.
They've never interacted before.
It seems hasty to assume it
directly relates to romance.
You're so level-headed, Kiyo-pon.
I could see it with Hirata-kun,
but not Yamauchi-kun so much, yeah.
Speaking of Hirata-kun,
I always figured he'd break up
with Karuizawa-san eventually.
What? Really?
They weren't exactly a great match.
I think Hirata-kun is more into
the quiet, beautiful type.
I always thought Karuizawa-san
was very pretty...
Don't you think so, Kiyotaka-kun?
I wouldn't know.
Well, the point is that
Hirata-kun is single now.
And there are quite a few girls
with their eyes on him.
Are there?
What, you never noticed?
Let's cut the gossip and
start studying for finals.
A failing score means expulsion, remember?
What, we have to do that now?
Message Received
Sender: Unlisted
Cancel
Open
Can't it wait?
Take this seriously.
Sorry to ask you to meet me like this.
It's fine.
Um...
You can call me Mii-chan.
Everyone else does.
That's a tall order.
All right.
What did you need?
Um... could you tell me about Hirata-kun?
Why ask me?
I'm not especially close to him.
But I hear you're the one
he relies on most of all!
Um... does Hirata-kun have his
eye on anyone in particular?
Probably not.
Really?!
I can't be entirely certain,
but Karuizawa only just broke
up with him, after all.
That's true.
Do you think I might have a chance with him?
I do.
But...
But...?
Hirata is a good person.
So he'll probably be cautious
about dating again.
He may be feeling guilty about
failing to make Karuizawa happy.
Yeah, Hirata-kun is nice like that.
If you go after him too quickly,
it may not turn out in your favor.
That's true.
Slow and steady, right?
Yes.
It's all about the one who laughs last.
I think I had the wrong idea
about you, Ayanokoji-kun.
The wrong idea?
You don't talk very much,
so I thought you'd be kind of scary.
But I think I see why
Hirata-kun relies on you.
You're really easy to talk to!
I feel like you were really
listening to every word I said.
Oh? Could this be...
Hiyori-chan?!
A date of some sort?
N-No! Of course not!
Then you wouldn't mind if I joined you?
Of course not!
Is that all right?
Yeah.
Well, what we were we talking about?
I was thinking of visiting China sometime.
Oh, because Mii-chan is a
Chinese exchange student, right?
Um... are you two friends?
Yes. We read together.
Well, that's technically correct.
I see!
It's great that you can make
friends in other classes.
I agree.
You can't have a real school life
if you're antagonistic all the time.
Sorry I'm late.
What's this all about?
It was hard to express via email.
Seems like I'm giving a lot of advice today.
There are strange rumors
swirling around Ichinose-san.
3rd Season
Classroom
of
the
Elite
Classroom of
the Elite
Rumors?
Put simply, they're slander.
What specifically do they say?
I summarized them here.
Incredible.
It feels malicious.
But the rumors are entirely baseless.
They could easily be written
off as the product of jealousy.
They're spreading among the
first-years too quickly for that.
Which suggests someone's actively
working to spread them?
Kanzaki-kun and the others from Class B
think the rumors originate with Class A.
Sakayanagi or Katsuragi, then?
It seems far too obvious for them.
That's the part that concerns me.
What if we assume there's
some truth to the rumor?
Even if the rest were completely made up,
that would greatly add to their plausibility.
Has Ichinose denied the rumors?
No, not as of yet.
We should wait and watch, then.
Even more so if they came from Class A.
We have no reason to intervene.
There's a chance it could make
Ichinose perceive us as enemies, too.
What would my brother do?
Sorry to call you over
this late, Ichinose-san.
Oh, no problem.
You're doing it because
you care about me, right?
You, too, Ayanokoji-kun. Thank you.
I'm just tagging along with Horikita, though.
It's about the rumors, right?
Yes. Do you have any idea
who's spreading them?
I can't say for certain, but I
think it might be Sakayanagi-san.
What makes you think that?
She kind of... declared war on me.
I guess that's not convincing
on its own, huh?
Class A has determined Class B
a threat worthy of destroying,
and is harming you by spreading
baseless rumors about you.
I'm not sure about that.
I think it should be up to you
whether you believe a rumor or not.
I feel like the best way to fight
Sakayanagi-san is to stay silent.
That will prevent collateral
damage to Class B and Class C.
You're a strong person.
You're thinking about not just yourself,
but the others around you, as well.
I don't think it's anything all that special.
Then let's work togeth—
Please don't get involved in this.
There's no need for you guys to get
on Sakayanagi-san's bad side, too.
You're sure about this?
Of course!
Thanks so much for worrying about me.
But I swear I'll be fine.
Thanks for having me by today.
Later!
Like I said before, we shouldn't get involved.
If Sakayanagi is the rumors' source,
we would put our own class in
the cross hairs by getting involved.
But if she takes Ichinose-san down,
she'll come after us next.
At which time Class B
will already be crushed.
That's beneficial to us.
You don't care what happens to Ichinose-san?
You're a very cold person.
Isn't that the stance you've always taken?
We'll eventually have to fight
and defeat her, regardless.
We have a common enemy right now.
We can take down Class A and
then duke it out with Class B.
Pure idealism.
I'm going, too.
See you later.
You're still here?
Could we talk a minute?
I don't know quite what to say...
I really am sorry.
For what?
It seems like those rumors have
you really worried about me.
I really don't want you
guys to worry, though.
Is that what you're telling
the members of Class B, too?
Yeah.
That's the line I'm sticking
to until the rumors go away.
That's all I had to say, so...
Thanks for listening.
See you!
Unregistered Number
Who is this?
Talk, or I'm hanging up.
Ayanokoji Kiyotaka.
Who are you?
They're making their move, then?
What is this?
Who put this in there?
What's going on here?
Let me look at that!
Something going on?
Ayanokoji?
A strange letter was placed
into all of our mailboxes.
This one.
"Ichinose Honami is a criminal."
The ridiculous rumors have spread this far.
After a blatant act like this,
the school will have to get involved.
And I'm sure the culprit is aware of that.
Y-You know who the culprit is?
I can't be certain, but...
Come on, you don't have to
grin and bear it like this.
Let's talk to the teachers.
It's getting really ridiculous!
Yeah. You're an innocent victim here.
It's fine.
This isn't enough to get to me.
Don't say that!
If you don't do something,
the rumors will just keep spreading!
Yeah, we need definitive action here.
Sooner or later it's all going to go too far!
Hey, can we talk?
You're from Class A, right?
Kamuro Masumi.
Your room is extremely plain.
That's the first thing you have to say
after forcing your way into my room?
Forcing my way?
I believe I got your permission.
So, what do you want?
It's going to be a long story,
so you should get me a drink.
Coffee or tea?
Do you have cocoa?
Yes.
I'll have that, then.
I offered two choices,
and she came up with a third one.
You're not drinking?
Are you wary of me?
Why wouldn't I be?
A girl I've never spoken to before—
one from Class A, at that—
is in my room.
You're not at all like
your classmate, Yamauchi.
What did you think of that
letter about Ichinose?
I didn't care.
Even if you didn't, you probably
thought about it, right?
Whether Ichinose is a good
person or a bad person?
Being a criminal doesn't necessarily
make you a bad person.
Sakayanagi knows a secret about Ichinose.
Really?
Just so you know, Sakayanagi doesn't
know I'm here talking to you about this.
I'm sure she'd be angry if she knew.
I'm afraid I don't believe you.
That's why I'm going to tell
you what Ichinose is hiding.
But first, I need to tell you
why Sakayanagi works me so hard.
It was after the entrance ceremony.
Wait a moment.
You shoplifted, didn't you?
So what if I did?
Your technique was impressive.
I'll return it.
Here.
You drink alcohol?
I don't actually, no.
So you did it purely for the thrill, then?
Why don't you just turn me
in to the school already?
Why don't you let me dispose of this?
If you won't call them, I will!
I like you, Kamuro Masumi-san.
I think I'll make you my first friend.
I was a habitual shoplifter.
"Was"?
I don't have time for it now.
Sakayanagi works me too hard for that.
That's why you came to me?
Yes.
Ichinose's secret is the same as mine.
She has a history of shoplifting?
Despite what a queen bee she is.
So you need to stop Sakayanagi.
You can make it happen, right?
Why me?
I don't have anyone to confide in.
And you're the person Sakayanagi
is most worried about.
I'm honored.
But I can't trust you.
Why not?
I could imagine Sakayanagi choosing to
sacrifice you to draw me into the fight.
I'll prove it, then.
See?
It does seem genuine.
Of course it is.
And it's not something a
student like me could buy.
I suppose I have to believe you.
I'm glad to hear it.
Good luck to you.
Take this with you.
Hey!
Horikita Manabu
Yes?
Ayanokoji.
I wanted to inform you of something.
What, is that real Valentine's chocolate?
Kushida Kikyo has made
contact with Nagumo Miyabi.
No, just obligation!
I see.